# **Tom Stannett**

**Engineering Masters Graduate** 

6 Northfield Shalford, Surrey, GU4 8JN (+44) 7596700788 invisibletree@protonmail.ch

#### **PERSONAL STATEMENT**

I am a recent Engineering Graduate with a passion for design, art and software development. I have extensive C++ and visual programming (OpenGL) experience, as well as heading many University web design and full stack development projects. I am a quick learner with a keen eye for detail and I am as happy working alone as in a team.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Natural Interactions Lab**, Oxford — *Junior Researcher*

JUNE 2019 - OCTOBER 2019

**Role:** Research and alpha design of novel prosthetic device for use in developing countries. Spent two weeks in India conducting device alpha testing in partnership with St John's Hospital, Bangalore.

**Skills:** C++, microcontroller and testbench circuit design, SolidWorks modelling, organisation and administration pertaining to arranging device trials and patients.

### **Cambertronics**, Cranleigh — *Junior Technician*

JULY 2016 - AUGUST 2016, JULY 2017 - AUGUST 2017

Role: Junior Factory Line Technician.

**Skills:** Working to strict quotas within deadlines, strong interpersonal and teamwork, flexibility and ability to learn quickly on the job.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Keble College, University of Oxford** Oxford — *Masters of Engineering 1st Class*

October 2016 - JUNE 2020

**Specialisations:** Machine Learning, Computer Engineering, Statistics, Data Science, Pure Mathematics.

**Bachelors Project:** Realtime Machine Learning for decoding patient intent for electromyographic prostheses. (C++, Python)

**Masters Project:** Deep Learned Convolutional Neural Network for solving Simultaneous Localisation And Mapping (SLAM) on a mobile robotics

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Programming: C++, Python, C#, OpenGL, TensorFlow Web-dev: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Node, Nunjucks, Jamstack (11ty), Tailwind DevOps: Github, Netlify OS: Arch Linux, Ubuntu, OSX, Windows

#### **NONTECHNICAL SKILLS**

Organisation: GitHub, AGILE

**Communication:** Presenting highly technical information to a non-technical audience.

Flexibility: Experience in working with large well structure teams as well as smaller more agile teams.

#### **VOLUNTEERING**

**Geovia Eco Commune:** A one month residency on a sustainable commune and farm.

platform using realtime LiDAR data. (C++, Tensorflow, OpenGL, Python).

- Involved working in the perception subgroup of the Dynamic Robotics System Group.
- Required tight version control on GitHub due to the size of the group and codebase.
- Heavy reliance on visualisation of testing data, requiring drawing of complex LiDAR scenes as well as applying realtime interactive transformations - C++, Python, OpenGL, 3D Geometry.
- Due to design requirements, high level of parallelism via threading was required.

## **Godalming College**, Godalming — 4 A-levels and EPQ

SEPTEMBER 2014 - JUNE 2016

**A-levels:** Maths (A\*), Further Maths (A\*), Physics (A\*), Computing (A\*)

**EPQ:** Hardware Implementations of Neuroplasticity for Machine Learning (A)

#### **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

**Portfolio (https://tm-stnt.dev)-** Find my web design & development portfolio here

## **Drain Zine (http://www.drainzine.fr)**— *University's first counter-cultural online zine*

Pitch: An online zine focusing on counter-cultural elements in fashion, music and art evoking early internet nostalgia through a combination of angelfire-esque visuals and a choose your own adventure format. Drain Zine edition 2 was delayed by Coronavirus and Finals, however is in the pipeline and massively overhauled in terms of visual aesthetic, interactivity, and content.

**Title:** Co-Founder, CTO, Co-Editor, Writer **Skills Used/Learned:** HTML5, CSS3, Node, 11ty, Jamstack, Google Analytics, GIMP, Submission Editing.

#### **Interests**

- I love web development, and enjoy making personal sites for my friends and projects
- I have a deep passion for music, and have been playing guitar for 12 years. I am also self taught on the drums and keyboard, and enjoy producing music in my spare time.
- I love to go rock climbing to keep me fit, street skateboarding and chess.